Darshanath Munasinghe

PROFILE

I'm a motivated, team-work oriented and responsible data analytics student at Hyper Island, Stockholm. My goal is to gain experience within this field and increase data efficiency to deliver insights and implement action-oriented solutions. CONTACT DETAILS

darshanath.munasinghe@ hyperisland.se

+46 73960 99 46

1998-11-11

B-körkort

https://www.linkedin.com/darshanath-munasinghe

EXPERIENCE

Data Engineer

Datia, Stockholm

Juni 2021 - Aug 2021

In a 3 months internship, I worked closely with datias data engineers and fetched data to their Amazon Warehouse with the help of Fetch APIs. MY CHARACTERISTICS

Creative

Problem solver

Fast learner

Curious

Serviceminded

Scrum Master

Gullersgrupp Hackathon, Stockholm

Sep 2020 - Sep 2020

I helped Gullersgrupp with a hackathon for the fashion store Indiska. I was the Scrum Master for a group. Using design techniques like Double Diamond and other tools from the Hyper Island toolbox, I did my best for my group to win the hackathon.

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

Google Analytics, SQL, Python, HTML, CSS, JS

Ground Handling

SAS Scandinavian Airlines, Gothenburg

Aug 2018 - Aug 2020

I worked with logistics and customer service. In the department, we worked with LEAN procedures and I learnt how to work efficiently without making major losses.

OTHER SKILLS

Adobe CC, Logic Pro, FL Studios

LANGUAGES

Swedish (native)

English (professionnal)

EDUCATION

Data Analyst

Hyper Island, Stockholm Aug 2020 - Aug 2022 INTERESTS

Data and design

Producing music

Working out

Natural Science Program

Aranäsgymnasiet, Kungsbacka

Aug 2014 - Jun 2017

REFERENCES

Sent upon request.